

Martin Šuba javascript developer

About

Software engineer developing applications in Javascript/Typescript focused on web technologies. Specializes in front-end part of applications and websites. Has experience with many aspects of webdevelopment such as working with front-end frameworks, Node.js, REST API, developing browser extensions, writing unit tests, refactoring and building responsive and pixel perfect websites.

Experience

Javascript Developer

SaferPass

October 2017 - Present Bratislava, Slovakia

Taking care of front-end part of SaferPass password manager browser extension. Mostly working with javascript/typescript, angularJS, web extension API, web API, node.js. Implementing new features as well as refactoring legacy code and writing unit tests.

Front-end web developer

WEZEO

September 2015 - September 2017 Bratislava, Slovakia

Building front-end of responsive cross-browser/platform web and mobile applications. Working mostly with HTML, SASS, Javascript, jQuery and frameworks like AngularJS, Angular and Ionic.

Front-end web developer

Elite Solutions

April 2014 - August 2015 Bratislava, Slovakia

Creating web sites and user interfaces using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Cooperating with graphic designers and back-end developers. Working for clients like O2, Sberbank, SLSP, VÚB and Hyundai.

Front-end web developer

pelicantravel.com

April 2013 - March 2014 Bratislava, Slovakia

I focused mainly on coding web pages, coding e-mail newsletters, customizing WordPress templates and some other online marketing activities.

Front-end coder

webikon

November 2012 - March 2013

Bratislava, Slovakia

Wordpress themes coding (HTML + CSS + jQuery)

Education

University of Economics in Bratislava

Management

2013 - 2015

Master's degree

University of Economics in Bratislava

Business Economics and Management

2010 - 2013

Bachelor's degree

Skills

development:			
Javascript	Ts TypeScript	⊚ Node.js	React / Redux
Angular	♦ Git	Webpack	mpm
Mocha	Jasmine	Travis	Ohrome Extensions
SASS			
language:			
English	Czech	Slovak	

other: